export default data = [
  {
      question: "Amy did not _____ changes in the course schedule and therefore missed the class.",
      options: ["arrest","alarm","notice","delay"],
      correct_option: "notice"
  },
  {
      question: "It is not easy for old people to _____ their backs, so they need help when their backs itch.",
      options: ["label","scratch","lighten","squeeze"],
      correct_option: "scratch"
  },
  {
      question: "Mary is suffering from a stomachache and needs to eat food which is easy to _____.",
      options: ["launch","invade","adopt","digest"],
      correct_option: "digest"
  },
  {
      question: "Since our classroom is not air-conditioned, we have to _____ the heat during the hot summer days.",
      options: ["consume","tolerate","recover","promote"],
      correct_option: "tolerate"
  },
  {
      question: "Sue is so _____ that she always breaks something when she is shopping at a store.",
      options: ["religious","visual","clumsy","intimate"],
      correct_option: "clumsy"
  },
  {
      question: "Ann enjoyed going to the flower market. She believed that the _____ of flowers refreshed her mind.",
      options: ["instance","dominance","appliance","fragrance"],
      correct_option: "fragrance"
  },
  {
      question: "The profits of Prince Charles’s organic farm go to _____ to help the poor and the sick.",
      options: ["charities","bulletins","harvests","rebels"],
      correct_option: "charities"
  },
  {
      question: "Jack was given the rare _____ of using the president’s office, which made others quite jealous.",
      options: ["mischief","privilege","involvement","occupation"],
      correct_option: "privilege"
  },
  {
      question: "This new computer is obviously _____ to the old one because it has many new functions.",
      options: ["technical","suitable","superior","typical"],
      correct_option: "superior"
  },
  {
      question: "Simon loves his work. To him, work always comes first, and family and friends are _____.",
      options: ["secondary","temporary","sociable","capable"],
      correct_option: "secondary"
  },
  {
      question: "Although your plans look good, you have to be _____ and consider what you can actually do.",
      options: ["dramatic","realistic","stressful","manageable"],
      correct_option: "realistic"
  },
  {
      question: "Built under the sea in 1994, the _____ between England and France connects the UK more closely with mainland Europe.",
      options: ["waterfall","temple","tunnel","channel"],
      correct_option: "tunnel"
  },
  {
      question: "This tour package is very appealing, and that one looks _____ attractive. I don’t know which one to choose.",
      options: ["equally","annually","merely","gratefully"],
      correct_option: "equally"
  },
  {
      question: "Hseu Fang-yi, a young Taiwanese dancer, recently _____ at Lincoln Center in New York and won a great deal of praise.",
      options: ["performed","pretended","postponed","persuaded"],
      correct_option: "performed"
  },
  {
      question: "The police searched the house of the suspect _____. They almost turned the whole house upside down.",
      options: ["relatively","thoroughly","casually","permanently"],
      correct_option: "thoroughly"
  },
]
